{
    "subject": "resource/Duffy_(singer)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Living_people",
    "human_readable": "Duffy is about Living people.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8771286010742188,
            "question": "Can Duffy provide insights into different cultures and perspectives through its coverage of living people?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8026841282844543,
            "question": "What might be some examples of information found in Duffy about a living person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7096392512321472,
            "question": "Is Duffy a reliable source for personal information about individuals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.618224024772644,
            "question": "What are some limitations of using Duffy to learn about people?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4863351285457611,
            "question": "Is Duffy helpful for researching current events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4352385997772217,
            "question": "Who are the subjects of information in Duffy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43338024616241455,
            "question": "How could Duffy be used to find out about a celebrity's recent activities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39718320965766907,
            "question": "Does Duffy contain information about fictional characters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3512200117111206,
            "question": "What kind of information does Duffy provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31668978929519653,
            "question": "Can Duffy be used to learn about historical figures?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Duffy is about Living people.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4776_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of information does Duffy provide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4776_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Duffy contain information about fictional characters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4776_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How could Duffy be used to find out about a celebrity's recent activities?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4776_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_156.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4776_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text documents discuss Carol Ann Duffy's life and work, including her poems and plays. Since she is a living person, the statement \"Duffy is about Living people\" is supported by the context. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for the answer being \"no\" is that based on the context information, it appears to be an introduction and a collection of articles about Carol Ann Duffy's life and work, but none of them mention whether she is still living or not."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe context information provided mentions Carol Ann Duffy as a living person, having been born on December 23, 1955. Therefore, the statement \"Duffy is about Living people\" is supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Duffy is a poet who wrote about addiction, specifically about someone named Duffy who struggled with opioids and other substances, implying that the subject matter involves non-living people or at least not living people in the sense of being healthy.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}